## PRASANNA PETHE Featured

MCA|5 years of experience in Software Development|Experienced working with Core Java, Collections |Proficient in technologies such as Spring boot, Hibernate, JavaScript/JQuery, Angular, Html, Rest Web Services, MySQL



Current Designation: Associate Software Developer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: AIT Global india pvt ltd Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune, Mumbai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Associate Software Developer, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Software Development, Software Engineering, Application Programming, Application Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Angular, Spring

Boot, Hibernate, Rest WS, Java 7, Oracle, MSSQL

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

## Summary

Full stack developer with 5+ years of experience, specialized in object-oriented approach to application development. Familiar with Web Application and wellversed in numerous technologies including Java 7, Spring Boot, hibernate and Angular. Passion to code and learn.

### **Work Experience**

AIT Global india pvt ltd as Associate Software Developer

Mar 2019 to Till Date

Cooperate with the team member and develop back end development.

Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

Design the database as per requirement from the client.

Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end websites as well as challenging back-end server code.

**Duraline india pvt ltd** as HR and Software Developer Feb 2017 to Mar 2019

Design and develop the database and application as per requirement from the Company. Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end websites as well as challenging back-end server code.

# Atharv security and manpower service (Contract) Duraline india pvt ltd as Software Developer Feb 2016 to Jan 2017

Design and develop the web application as per requirement from the Company. Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end websites as well as challenging back-end server code.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Chemistry) from Padmabhushan Vasantdada Patil Mahavidyalaya in 2007

PG: MCA (Computers) from jayawant institute of management studies in 2011

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
JAVA	8	2020	4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
HTML		2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
JavaScript		2020	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
Angular	8	2019	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
Hibernate		2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
MySQL		2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
Linux	18	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
springboot	2	2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
ENGLISH	Proficient			
HINDI	Expert			
MARATHI	Expert			

## **Affirmative Action**

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

#### **Work Authorization**

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time